Subindex build by Linnet
http://linnet.126.com  http://blog.csdn.net/redbirdli
火鸟字幕合并器SubindexV0.5
Created time 12.09.29 07:23:18
"天才理论传" 前情提要
Previously on  The Big Bang Theory...
我们正式宣布你们结为夫妻!
We now pronounce you husband and wife!
我超爱这段!
I love this part!
我也是!
Me,too!
我很纠结
I have strongly mixed feelings!
Howard真的上太空了
So,Howard's really in space,huh?
恩 国际空间站
Mm-hmm,International Space Station.
两百五十英里远
250 miles that way.
现在 Howard正像个迷你犹太神 一样看着我们的地球
Right now,Howard's staring down at our planet like a tiny Jewish Greek god.
宙斯维茨 (犹太名常用后缀)
Zeusowitz.
我必须承认 我禁不住有点嫉妒
I must admit,I can't help but feel a twinge of envy.
他转向窗外 就能看到壮丽的宇宙
He can look out the window and see the majesty of the universe unfolding before his eyes.
透过他那暗淡迷茫的眼睛
His dim,uncomprehending eyes.
像只机场行李箱的小猫一样
It's like a cat in an airport carrying case.
其实上面也没那么好
You know,it's not exactly glamorous up there.
他们的饮用水是 用别人的尿液里过滤而来的
The water that the astronauts drink is made from each other's recycled urine.
听起来不错
Must be nice.
我尿出来的肯定没人想喝
Nobody wants anything that comes out of  me.
我很想知道他现在在干吗
I wonder what he's doing right this very second.
恩 也许在零重力状态下做实验
Mm,conducting experiments in zero gravity.
通过望远镜探视宇宙的起源
Peering through his telescope at the birth of the cosmos.
不管做什么 他的人生已经大不相同了
Whatever it is,we know his life will never be the same.
Howard! 你能听见吗?
Howard! Can you hear me?!
不用电话都能听见!
I can hear you  without  the phone!
不要凶我
Don't be snippy.
和我宝贝通话 我太激动了!
I'm just excited to talk to my baby!
和你通话 我也很激动
I'm excited to talk to you,too.
听说你疯了 要搬出去 和那小波兰女孩一起住
So,what's this  mishegas  about you moving out to go live with the little Polish girl?!
她现在是我妻子好不好?
How about calling her my wife?
妻子是不会从丈夫他妈那儿 抢走儿子的
Wives don't take boys from their mothers.
当然会的
They do.
不然结婚干吗!
That's why we marry them!
希望你回来之前 我不会心碎而死
I just hope I'm not dead from a broken heart before you get back.
妈 不要这样
Ma,please.
整个NASA的人都听着这通电话呢
Everyone from NASA is listening to this phone call.
很好 应该让他们知道 你是个多么不孝的儿子
Good. They should know what a horrible son you are!
好吧 妈 很高兴和你聊 挂了
Okay,Ma,great talking to you!Gotta go!
好了 太空生活也毁了
Well... space is ruined.
-=伊甸园美剧  http://bbs.sfile2012.com=- -=伊甸园字幕站  http://ytet.org/=- 荣誉出品 本字幕仅供学习交流，严禁用于商业途径
=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-   proudly presents
-=YTET-伊甸园字幕组=- 翻译:Elequent 大布 桦桦 许块块 Junson 校对: 阿公 时间轴:  邦德猪
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- sync:邦德猪
the big bang theory Season06Episode01 720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
太让人兴奋了
This is so exciting.
很快 我的上唇就会 和我漂亮闺蜜的假金发一样美了
Soon,my upper lip will be the same fake blonde as my beautiful best friend.
嘿 我的头发本来就是这个颜色
Hey,this is my natural hair color.
现在是
Now.
明晚Sheldon有没有什么特殊安排?
So,does Sheldon have anything special planned for you tomorrow night?
有的
Oh,yes.
根据"交往协议" 在我们首次约会的周年纪念日
According to the Relationship Agreement,on the anniversary of our first date,
他必须带我出去吃顿好的 问我过得如何
he must take me to a nice dinner,ask about my day
来点身体接触 让别人误以为我们在亲热
and engage in casual physical contact that a disinterested onlooker might mistake for intimacy.
好刺激
That's hot.
你们得做好防护措施
You kids better use protection.
还要多久?
How long does this stay on?
几分钟就好了
Just a couple of minutes.
你以前没弄过?
You've really never done this before?
高中时候弄过一次 但我中途打瞌睡 醒来脸就成二度化学烧伤了
Once in high school,but I dozed off and woke up with second-degree chemical burns on my face.
天哪 太悲剧了
Oh,my gosh,that's awful.
其他孩子笑话你了吗?
The other kids make fun of you?
没 我骗他们说是疱疹
No,I had a cover story; I told everyone it was herpes.
你和Leonard最近咋样?
So,how's everything going with you and Leonard?
我也不知道 还是很诡异
I don't know,it's still kind of weird.
还没从他做爱时 向我求婚那事缓过来
We haven't really recovered since he proposed to me in the middle of sex.
真悲剧
Boo-hoo.
如果Sheldon在做爱时向我求婚 我的子宫会紧抓住他 永不放手
If Sheldon proposed to me during sex,my ovaries would grab on to him and never let go.
Leonard 你怎么看"人择原理"
Leonard,where do you stand on the anthropic principle?
很有趣
Interesting question.
一方面 我认为...
On the one hand,I always thought...
你都不知道是什么吧?
You don't even know what it is,do you?
"人择原理"是指如果我们要解释 为什么宇宙是现在这样
The anthropic principle states that if we wish to explain why our universe exists the way it does,
答案就是正因为有这样的宇宙...
the answer is that it must have qualities
人类这种智慧物种才会存在 才有能力来问这个问题
that allow intelligent creatures to arise who are capable of asking the question.
比如我现在这么流利地表达
As I am doing so eloquently right now.
我知道"人择原理"是什么
I know what the anthropic principle is.
当然 我刚给你解释了啊
Of course.I just explained it to you.
你怎么看?
Now,where do you stand on it?
Where do you stand on it?
非常赞成
Strongly pro.
那么我相信上帝用六天创造了世界 然后第七天创造了你来烦我
Then I believe that God created the world in six days,and on the seventh,he made you to annoy me.
嘿 哥们
Hey,guys.
等等 Raj 你怎么看"人择原理"?
Yeah,wait,Raj,where do you stand on the anthropic principle?
完全赞同
I'm all for it.
好样的
Attaboy!
等等
Well,hang on.
为什么你认为他知道 而我却不知道
Why do you believe that he knows what it is and I don't?
哦 Leonard
Oh,Leonard.
咱别自讨没趣好吗
Let's not take a saw to the branch we're sitting on,shall we?
嘿 你们晚上有空的话
Hey,uh,if you guys are free tonight,
有个温泉浴场 你把脚浸到水里 会有很多小鱼来吃脚上的死皮
I heard about a spa where you soak your feet in a pool full of little fish that eat all the dead skin right off them.
不用我提醒吧 洛杉矶的凉鞋季节马上来咯
I don't need to tell you,in Los Angeles,sandal season is year round.
我和Penny有约
Actually,I'm hanging out with Penny.
好吧
Oh,okay.
那就只剩下我们俩了 Sheldon
Sounds like it's me and you,Sheldon.
咱一起去让孔雀鱼吃吃脚吧?
How about we sic some guppies on those puppies?
我已经重复无数遍了
As I've stated before on numerous occasions,
在所有海洋生物里 我只愿意被海妖吃掉
the only sea creature I would even consider being eaten by is the Kraken,
因为那样我生前听到的 最后一句话就是"放出海妖"
because the last words I would hear are: "Release the Kraken.
(电影"诸神之战"经典台词)
***
每听必嗨
" That never gets old.
"放出海妖" 好爽
"Release the Kraken!" Oh,chills.
再说 我今晚要与Amy共进晚餐
Besides,I'm having dinner with Amy.
好啊
Oh,okay.
那我就回家 一个人待着好了
I'll just go home and be alone.
其实挺不错的
W-Which is cool.
我一个人吃饭 一个人睡觉 一个人哭...
I eat alone,I sleep alone,I cry alone,so...
真不错
Cool.
见鬼 如果你不忙的话 可以加入我们
Darn. If you weren't busy,I'd ask you to join us.
真的吗? 我也能来? 谢谢!
Really? I can come?Thanks!
Sheldon 你真得要带着Raj 去和Amy约会吗?
Sheldon,are you sure you want to be bringing Raj on your date night with Amy?
当然了
Oh,absolutely.
我和Amy的协议中有规定 我要向她提供交流和身体接触
I have a contractual obligation to provide Amy with conversation and casual physical contact,
但并没有说明我不能外包给印度人
but nowhere is it specified that I can't outsource that to an Indian.
(印度是外包业大国)
***
Howie?
嘿 我美貌如花的老婆!
Hey,there's my beautiful bride!
看得见我吗?
Can you see me?
看得见
I can.
你还好吗?
How are you?
棒极了
I'm amazing.
比我梦里的还要好
I mean,this is even better than I dreamed.
我向窗外看去...
I look out the window,and...
太不可思议了
it's all so unbelievable.
真好
Good for you.
我刚刚和你妈吃了顿马拉松晚餐
I just had a seemingly endless dinner with your mom.
是吗? 挺好的呀
Oh,yeah? That's nice.
一开始是的
It was.
直到我发现你没告诉她 我们不会跟她住
Until I found out you never told her we're not gonna live with her.
我们来谈谈这事吧
Let's talk about  that  for a minute.
看啊 这支笔漂起来了
Hey,look,this pen is floating.
多疯狂啊
How crazy is that?
你说已经告诉她了 根本没有!
You said you told her,but you never did!
好吧 我知道你很失望
Okay,okay,I know you're upset,but...
但让我分享一下 我到这边之后学到的
let me share something I've learned since I got here.
从太空看下来 你就明白自己的问题有多么微不足道
You realize how small your problems are when you're looking down on them from space.
好受些了吧
Now,come on,that's got to make you feel better.
我在你的屏幕上清楚吗?
How clear is the image of me on that screen?
挺清楚的
Pretty clear.
那我看起来像是好点了吗?
Do I  look  like I feel better?
视频也不是太高清啦
I mean,it's not,like,HD quality.
听着 先生 你要去告诉你妈 解决这事
Listen,mister,you're gonna talk to your mother and you're gonna fix this,
否则你回来之后 我说要做的那事 你就自行解决吧
or that thing I said I was gonna do to you the minute you got home,you can do to yourself.
他到了这儿之后就没少干
Like he's been doing since he got here.
Sheldon 这地方真浪漫
Sheldon,this place is so romantic.
我很高兴你喜欢
Oh,I'm glad you like it.
是Raj选的
Raj picked it out.
看到他的话 替我说声谢谢
Well,when you see him,tell him I say thank you.
你自己说吧
Tell him yourself.
亲爱的们!
Yoo-hoo!
在这儿呢!
Over here!
我不理解 他在这儿干吗?
I don't understand.What's he doing here?
我请他来的
I invited him.
参加我们的约会?
On our date?
Sheldon 这样不对
Sheldon,that's not okay.
很对
Yes,it is.
交往协议里有一处漏洞
There's a loophole in the Relationship Agreement.
你找到个漏洞?
You found a loophole?
对不起 我先点单了
Sorry I started without you.
我有点紧张
I'm a little nervous.
哥很久没约会了
It's been a long time since I've been on a date.
真不敢相信 我还漂白了唇毛
I can't believe I bleached my mustache for this.
你应该去我姐们那儿
You should go to my girl.
她还会帮你免费修鬓角
She'll knock out those sideburns for free.
你知道吗 Amy 我们俩还没有真正交流过
You know,Amy,I don't even think you and I have had a real conversation.
今晚是个进一步认识的好机会
Let's use tonight to get to know each other a little better.
你先来
You start.
滚回家去
Go home.
我不明白
I don't understand.
Sheldon 你怎么能这样做? 今天是我们两周年纪念日
Sheldon,how could you do this?It's our second anniversary.
是你们的纪念日?!
It's your anniversary?!
天啊 我不知道
Oh,my God,I had no idea.
Amy 请让我来弥补
Amy,please,let me make this right.
谢谢
Thank you.
这是我的荣幸
My pleasure.
服务生? 来一瓶香槟 外加三个杯子
Waiter?A bottle of champagne and three glasses.
这太浪漫了吧?
Oh,boy,isn't this romantic?
我希望这是句反问句 因为我没感觉
Oh,I hope that's a rhetorical question,because I have no clue.
真不错
This is great.
是为了什么事?
What's the occasion?
没什么
No occasion.
就是我们之间最近不是很顺
You know,things have been a little weird between us,
所以我想单独为你 准备一个"快乐之夜"
so I wanted to throw together a fun night just for you.
你想得真周到
That is so sweet.
都是你喜欢的 啤酒 鸡翅 迷你汉堡
I got all your favorites.Beer,wings,sliders.
我们可以看橄榄球赛
We can watch the football game.
我还在肚皮上画了东西
I even painted my stomach.
"加油 运动"?
"Go sports"?
这个嘛...
Well...
万一你想看棒球 我不想太尴尬
in case you were in the mood for baseball,I didn't want to look ridiculous.
太棒了 我喜欢!
This is awesome.I love it!
那就好
Good,I'm glad.
天啊 我今天忙晕了 这正是我想要的
Gosh,I worked my ass off today.This is exactly what I needed.
太好了 放松享受吧 今晚是你的
Great.Just relax and enjoy.Tonight is all about you.
谢啦!
Ah,thank you!
那么 我们到底是什么关系呢?
So,where exactly are we in this relationship?
不是吧!
Oh,come on!
我刚告诉你今天很累
I just told you I had a hard day.
是的 很抱歉 看球赛吧!
You're right,I'm sorry.Let's watch the game.
很好
Great.
我发现越刻意不提 越奇怪
I just know the longer we wait to talk about it,the weirder it gets.
亲 今晚让我当个妹子好不?
Sweetie,can I just be the girl tonight?
当然 你是妹子 我是汉子
Absolutely.You're the girl,I'm the guy.
好好看球赛吧 我给你弄点吃的
Now,you watch your football game while I make you a little plate here.
谢了!
Thank you!
我去开
Oh,I'll get it.
加油 运动!
Go sports!
你好-好-好
Hello-lo-lo.
你怎么在这儿?
What are you doing here?
你不是跟Sheldon和Amy一起吗?
I thought you were out th Sheldon and Amy.
没错 但今天是他俩周年纪念 我不想当电灯泡
I was,but it's their anniversary and I didn't want to be a third wheel,
所以我决定参加你和Penny的约会
so I figured I'd come over here and hang out with you and Penny on your date.
嗯 只怕时机不对
Well,it's not really a great time.
Penny和我有些事要谈
Penny and I have some things we need to talk about.
没啊 没事! 进来吧!
No,we don't!Come on in!
太好了!
Sweet!
真不敢相信 我还为今晚剃了肚毛
I can't believe I shaved my stomach for this.
嘿 水果圈
Hey,Froot Loops.
有电话找你
You got a phone call.
谁?
Who is it?
一个自称你妈的人 但听起来像你爸
A woman who says she's your mother but sounds like your father.
嘿 妈
Hey,Ma.
如果你打开电脑 我们可以视频
You know,we could see each other if you turn on the computer.
我可不会靠近那怪东西
I'm not going near that fakakta thing.
我会中电脑病毒的!
I'll catch a computer virus!
你中不了电脑病毒
You can't catch a computer virus.
这么说除了是宇航员 你还是医生?
Oh,so now you're an astronaut  and  a doctor?
什么事 妈?
What do you want,Ma?
你老婆说 你有事要告诉我
Your wife says you have something important to tell me.
好吧 是这么回事
Okay,here it is.
Bernadette和我要开始 共同生活了 并且...
Bernadette and I are starting a life together and...
噢 天哪!
Oh,God!
你真要离开我!
You  are  gonna leave me!
妈...
Ma...
没事
It's okay.
你爸离开了我 你离开我 我想我就是天生遭人弃的命
Your father left me,you left me-- I guess I'm just the kind of person people like to leave.
还没...
It's not...
确定 我会跟Bernadette谈谈
definite.I'll talk to Bernadette.
不用了
Don't bother.
我会找个地洞待着 死了不会麻烦别人
I'll just go sit in a hole in the ground so I'm no trouble when I die.
别说了 妈
Stop it,Ma.
我保证会让Bernie回心转意的
I'm sure I can get Bernie to come around.
我就知道!
I knew it!
我就知道她是幕后主使!
I knew she was behind this!
听着 如果你是男人 就别受女人摆布
You listen to me,if you want to be a man,you can't let a woman tell you what to do!
好好
Okay,okay.
不敢相信他们这群人 竟然赢了冷战
I can't believe these people won the Cold War.
换个话题好不?
Now,can we please change the subject?
好 解释下为什么 那么久都没给我写封信
Fine. Explain why   you've been gone so long and I haven't gotten   a single letter.
连张破明信片都没有!
Not even a lousy postcard!
我开始喜欢橄榄球了
You know,I'm growing to like American football.
是啊 很有意思 不是吗?
Yeah,it's fun,isn't it?
嗯...
Well...
虽说没羽毛球或板球那么刺激 但嘿...
it's not the balls-to-the-wall action of badminton or cricket,but hey...
其它哪有刺激的了?
what is?
好吧 谁还要喝?
All right,who's ready for another beer?
我可以了 谢了
I'm good.No,thank you.
俩妹子
Girls.
我今晚好开心
I am having the nicest time.
你们像我的家人一样
You guys are like family to me.
你知道的 对吧?
You know that,right?
很好 你可以走了
That's great.Get out.
什么? 为啥啊?
What? Why?
Penny和我有些事要谈
Penny and I have some issues we need to talk about.
去你的破事吧!
Oh... pish on your issues!
你们没事
You guys are fine.
是的 你一路碰了些钉子
Yes,you hit some bumps along the way.
Penny 你一向知道这家伙对你有意思 但你却让他一直很卑微
I mean,Penny,you've always known how this man has felt about you,but you made him grovel for affection.
好吧 等等...
Okay,hold on...
不用自责
Now,don't blame yourself.
他卑微习惯了
He was a groveler from way back.
重点是 你们都走过来了
But the point is,the two of you got past it.
Leonard你在做爱时 向这可怜的女孩儿求婚?
And,Leonard,you go and propose to this poor girl in the middle of sex?
这都可以醒酒了
That was some weak tea,dude.
某些人会认为这样很浪漫
Some people might say it was romantic.
真的吗 不可能
Yeah,no.
但只要你们还在一起
But yet,here you two are,still together.
尽管我俩还有过疯狂裸体夜
And that's even after you and I had our crazy naked night.
- 好了... - 闭嘴
- Okay... - That's enough.
我是说 看你们经历了那么多
I'm just saying that after everything you've been through,
你们得深情对视 互诉爱意
you get to look into each other's eyes and say "I love you."
这才叫浪漫
And that's beautiful.
事实上 时至今日 她都没对我说过
Actually,to this day,she's never really said it.
Penny 这也太荒唐了
Oh,Penny!That's ridiculous!
你知道你是爱他的
You know you love him!
看着他的眼睛说我爱你
You look him in the eyes and you say it.
- Raj... - 快说吧 你知道你想说的
- Raj... - Oh,come on,you know you want to say it.
说出来 说你爱他
Say it. Say you love him.
说啊
Say it!
我真心以为她会说的
I really thought she would say it.
我之前有跟你说过 你像只性感的螳螂吗
Have I ever told you you're like a sexy praying mantis?
每次你喝了酒都这么说
Every time you drink alcohol.
你知道螳螂有什么迷人之处吗
You know what's wonderful about the praying mantis?
他们会吃掉他们的伴侣
They devour their mate.
你的意思是?
Your point being?
享用"点心"吧
Dessert is served.
我刚吃过水果馅饼
I just had cobbler.
你知道吗
You know what?
我们受够了
I'm done with this.
你要去哪儿
W-Where are you going?
我要离开了
I'm leaving.
你不能离开
You can't leave.
我需要你
I need you.
- 真的吗 - 当然
- You do? - Yes.
你还要载我呢
You're my ride.
Sheldon 如果你不发自内心说几句 我们就完了
Sheldon,you either say something meaningful and from the heart,or you and I are done.
好吧
All right.
请坐
Please.
Amy 当你我目光对视的刹那
Amy... when I look in your eyes and you're looking back in mine,
一切事物都不再平凡
everything feels not quite normal,
因为我既感到强大 又感到弱小
because I feel stronger and weaker at the same time.
既兴奋又惊恐
I feel excited and,at the same time,terrified.
事实上 我已不清楚我的感受
The truth is,I don't know what I feel,except...
我只知道我想做个什么人
I know what kind of man I want to be.
Sheldon
Sheldon...
这太惊艳了
that was beautiful.
我知道
I should hope so.
这是蜘蛛侠第一部里面的台词
That's from the first Spider-Man movie.
我接受了
I'll take it.
很好
Good.
现在我们可以AA了吧
Now,I assume we're splitting the check?
嘿 Stuart
Hey,Stuart.
我正准备打烊的
I was actually just about to close up.
抱歉 我马上就走
Oh,I'm sorry.I'll leave.
不 不 没事
No,no. It's okay.
- 随便看看吧 - 可以吗
- Hang out. - You sure?
嗯 你是我今天的第一位顾客
Yeah,you're my first customer today.
好吧 太好了
All right. Great.
我准备了晚饮
I'm,uh,having a nightcap.
想来一点吗
You want to join me?
喝的啥?
What are you drinking?
咖啡利口酒 用楚巴卡杯装的哦
Coffee liqueur in a Chewbacca mug.
("星战"中的人物)
***
我管它叫伤心蒂尼
I call it a sad-tini.
很配我今晚的经历 来一杯吧 谢了
Perfect for the night I'm having.Thank you.
有人陪喝真是好啊
Nice not to drink alone.
还真是
Amen to that.
有时我会往狗狗的餐盘里 倒点夏敦埃酒
Sometimes I pour a little chardonnay into my dog's water bowl.
开什么玩笑
You're kidding.
她发酒疯可不得了 但又有什么办法呢?
She's kind of a mean drunk,but what are you gonna do?
- 干杯 - 走一个
- Cheers. - Cheers.
来点音乐?
A little music?
好啊
Sure.
Bossa Nova
Bossa nova.
听到这旋律 屁屁忍不住摆动起来呢
You listen to that with your hips as well as your ears.
这就是...
Something about...
这拉丁的曲子让我觉得 身处里约的沙滩上
Latin music just makes me feel like I'm on a white sand beach in Rio.
是啊
Yeah.
那阳光 那海浪 那婀娜胴体 小麦肤色 汗水在阳光下闪闪发光
The sun,the waves,the beautiful bodies,tanned and glistening with sweat.
我该闪了
I should go.
谢谢你的酒
Yeah.Uh,thank you for the drink.
小意思
No problem.
- 嘿 Stuart - 怎么了?
- Hey,Stuart. - Yeah?
你愿意...
Do you want to...
明晚出来玩玩 吃点东西 看个电影吗?
hang out tomorrow night,maybe grab a bite to eat or catch a late movie?
好啊 听着不错 不过我最近手头比较紧
Yeah,I-I'd like to,but I'm a little tight on funds.
不用担心 我请客
No problem.My treat.
那我下班之后就过来
I'll swing by after work.
- 这么定了 - 好嘞
- Okay. - Okay.
约会也不是不可以
I could do worse.
好消息啊 Howie
Aw,that's such   good news,Howie.
谢谢你跟你妈说了
Thank you for telling her.
嘿 我可是大男人 当然得和老婆住一起
Hey,I'm a grown man; I'm gonna live with my wife.
我妈只是需要时间适应一个人
My mother's just gonna have to learn to make do on her own.
那她很难过吗?
Was she upset?
谁知道呢
Who can tell?
她什么不都是大喊吗
She yells everything.
她也许很难过
She might have been upset.
或者她只是饿了
She might have been hungry.
谢谢你说清这一切
Thanks for fixing it.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你哦
I love you,too.
好梦哦 明天再聊好吗?
Sweet dreams.I'll talk to you tomorrow?
晚安 飞天男
Good night,Rocket Man.
永远爱你爱你哟 宝贝
To infinity and beyond,baby.
圈圈
Loops.
你知道你在欺娘骗媳吗?
You realize you just lied your ass off to your wife  and  your mother.
嗯哪
I know.
那你回地球还活不活了
What are you gonna do when you get back to Earth?
我就没打算回去
Oh,I'm never going back.
-------------------------------------- 本论坛字幕仅翻译交流学习之用 禁止任何商业用途否则后果自负 -------------------------------------
=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- -=http://ytet.org=-   proudly presents
天才理论传 第六季 第一集 完 720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo
-=http://bbs.sfileydy.com=- sync:邦德猪 720p版本调校：C.Ronaldo